date,title,text,source,url,ticker,publisher,query,article_length,word_count,collection_date,finbert_label,finbert_score,finbert_sentiment,vader_compound,vader_label,textblob_polarity,textblob_label,date_only,spacy_entities_json,bert_entities_json,all_entities_json,num_entities,num_orgs,num_persons,num_locations
2026-01-18 12:19:48,American Express Company $AXP Shares Acquired by Nations Financial Group Inc. IA ADV - MarketBeat,American Express Company $AXP Shares Acquired by Nations Financial Group Inc. IA ADV&nbsp;&nbsp;MarketBeat,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2wFBVV95cUxOc0RtWnVJa2lEMFRJSXZRbVkwV1FIakpuNjBqUlE4c0dES2dIR3BxWENCd1NzdkQtZjhLRUpJY0ZzUDdFNHFVSnNxQmw5RE90aVpkcU1LWXFSNjN3S2doNlZUVmRxNVdGZjA0MndFVlVxN0dMX1gxQ3I0RmludTA2WWMwd3FtMWNzcXNGaVh6bVc3VnlzUlZjWHpyN2ZBM2MwNnY0eWc0QWVCRDNPQ2RWY1lpc3BiUElpYzlYVDltRi0tbi1tdlBHaHBwYm45OXNCdHdOYTRpd013eDQ?oc=5,AXP,,AXP stock news,106,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.296,0.296,0.296,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-18,"[{""text"": ""American Express Company $AXP Shares"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 36}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 49, ""end"": 77}, {""text"": ""IA"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 78, ""end"": 80}]","[{""text"": ""American Express Company"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9992806315422058, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 24}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9993277192115784, ""start"": 49, ""end"": 76}, {""text"": ""IA AD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8623384833335876, ""start"": 78, ""end"": 83}, {""text"": ""MarketBeat"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.936427116394043, ""start"": 96, ""end"": 106}]","[{""text"": ""American Express Company $AXP Shares"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""IA"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""American Express Company"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""IA AD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""MarketBeat"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,6,0,1
2026-01-18 12:15:12,Apple stock price slips to $255 ahead of a holiday-shortened week — AAPL earnings are the next test - TechStock²,Apple stock price slips to $255 ahead of a holiday-shortened week — AAPL earnings are the next test&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQODJZMVExWFJXSFpxWUN3S3ZBQ0VyeUVFVncxVHBweEhyRjVHemxUcmIxWEdIX3RmWDZRWnVaZW4yTThpdklMT3BVUUlEVUtIZGZOeUJyMWRGSk9rQVNwNTNmLTQ0elQ2MHp4ZV9uaWMxVUpKNVhvNUdYYlhzUEZWdFVWTlBOTFNFYnBybG83RFJscG1RTVBNeDZzaDVsY1dhR25paXlVSW43OVRCT01MTERNZHRzbk5F?oc=5,AAPL,,AAPL stock news,121,18,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-18,"[{""text"": ""Apple"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 5}, {""text"": ""255"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 28, ""end"": 31}, {""text"": ""test&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 95, ""end"": 121}]","[{""text"": ""Apple"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9914073348045349, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 5}, {""text"": ""S"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6595770716667175, ""start"": 115, ""end"": 116}]","[{""text"": ""Apple"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""255"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""test&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Apple"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""S"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,4,0,0
2026-01-18 12:00:26,Amgen Inc. (NASDAQ:AMGN) is largely controlled by institutional shareholders who own 80% of the company - Yahoo Finance,Amgen Inc. (NASDAQ:AMGN) is largely controlled by institutional shareholders who own 80% of the company&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxPVkp3RkpfNks1WVRSOXRfRXZ1X0QtdFU0c1k1NktZbmUwU1RGZE1rZXhDMXJqVURhaURmcGpnV0YwTjRJczY0Q0luRE5uSWJJR3M1YzBLNWhKbGxXUHppWDY5QkE4OVZJRjI3al9ZaXhGWnpfNUFHOXU0eThPOEQ1dQ?oc=5,AMGN,,AMGN stock news,128,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.4071428571428571,positive,2026-01-18,"[{""text"": ""Amgen Inc."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 10}, {""text"": ""AMGN"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 19, ""end"": 23}, {""text"": ""80%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""start"": 85, ""end"": 88}, {""text"": ""the company&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 92, ""end"": 128}]","[{""text"": ""Amgen Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9992440342903137, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 9}, {""text"": ""AM"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6150994896888733, ""start"": 19, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9973828792572021, ""start"": 115, ""end"": 128}]","[{""text"": ""Amgen Inc."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AMGN"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""80%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""the company&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Amgen Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AM"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,5,1,0
2026-01-18 11:43:58,BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print Guides For Mid-Single Digit NII Growth In FY26 - Menafn,BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print Guides For Mid-Single Digit NII Growth In FY26&nbsp;&nbsp;Menafn,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxQcmhhU3d4cE9tb21hLUlBMktzdVdpZ25SZlNaUlZWbG5HSmN0Y3ZMcEdzZ19zQjdTbmVZenFWb2dOZHFkNlZrRU1nbDNIb3Y4TmxoRjk3UmU0ZXJ4cTlUdmFpYTgteWEwWDNUUnhQT2licm5hTEw4VmdGWE9raFBhUEhROWY2WlNJNTk2bGFJMUtWZThNVkVNYkhSbkZFUG5oUUdwemY2NmtLQ2hoNFowZHFB?oc=5,BAC,,BAC stock news,100,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.6124,0.6124,0.6124,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-18,"[{""text"": ""BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print Guides"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 42}, {""text"": ""FY26&nbsp;&nbsp;Menafn"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 78, ""end"": 100}]",[],"[{""text"": ""BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print Guides"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""FY26&nbsp;&nbsp;Menafn"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}]",2,1,0,1
2026-01-18 11:26:14,Strong Analyst Confidence in Alibaba Group Holding (BABA) Amid AI and Cloud Momentum - Finviz,Strong Analyst Confidence in Alibaba Group Holding (BABA) Amid AI and Cloud Momentum&nbsp;&nbsp;Finviz,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxNNDJaZFJNNGQ1X2hWY0dyZTdfZnJFMmxfcFUtbkU3ck0zUmtReHcwRWRnTW9yd2RpMVpZVkpmYjVwNHdTZmdKT3dNc2x1bkpscFI3TkVxNGZqWl9SSlBPY2Ytem5QRzVkRGVKd3Z0QTFna0JkSlB3a1pqNWtpLXZheERybW0xb0h1MEtaeU5GUGp2NWF4Z1J4MG9JVC00TldxTUZaS2hvZkUyM29LcF9jbWd0TQ?oc=5,BABA,,BABA stock news,102,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.765,0.765,0.765,positive,0.4333333333333333,positive,2026-01-18,"[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 29, ""end"": 50}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9990648031234741, ""start"": 29, ""end"": 50}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9917346239089966, ""start"": 52, ""end"": 56}, {""text"": ""Moment"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5641540288925171, ""start"": 76, ""end"": 82}, {""text"": ""vi"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6775946617126465, ""start"": 99, ""end"": 101}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Moment"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""vi"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,5,0,0
2026-01-18 06:02:38,Abbott Laboratories (ABT) Positioned to Benefit as Healthcare Sector Enters Recovery Phase - Finviz,Abbott Laboratories (ABT) Positioned to Benefit as Healthcare Sector Enters Recovery Phase&nbsp;&nbsp;Finviz,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNc0ZQV2ZYMklYcWdaY2hTUThWejR1U181U3YwUEJiM3Y0cjJqUExLZmlySlVrTHY1QjZ0SHpjUFVNRnNRa3JuSkptRlJ0UUdkVnJvV2JHSGlUbVNHQ2lJYWFZcFhINEhXUFZpQkIzOU5HQ2YwTnVWZUNsbmhsNV9paFhjeWxaWHV6eDRQSDdXWHB4N01INi16MDF3UXc4dTFCWkt2Nll5WHZna0ptaWN6YTRlTTFROE1hYlI0?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,108,12,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.4588,0.4588,0.4588,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-18,"[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 19}, {""text"": ""ABT) Positioned to Benefit"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 21, ""end"": 47}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9992720484733582, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 19}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9903544187545776, ""start"": 21, ""end"": 24}, {""text"": ""Healthcare Sector"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7951030135154724, ""start"": 51, ""end"": 68}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""ABT) Positioned to Benefit"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Healthcare Sector"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,5,0,0
2026-01-17 23:07:57,AMD stock price rises into long weekend as $311 million data-center lease puts AI demand in focus - TechStock²,AMD stock price rises into long weekend as $311 million data-center lease puts AI demand in focus&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxOdVNKdlJuTWdEYndwQmlsaHlDT0I2Zk1BamdwRzNsaWZSNzZLUVRlSnVWTkdUMkVoenc1RjRZY0EyenJRNEd5UWxhS3cxZDY2d0h3WmdXWjJ6bVVXcXdiMkt0a2VVYWt6WERtRVR2dHBKaW5sQXR1ZHptYmg3T3dvYlUxbEhHMU41NndnSldvV3U2NFlFbFZQYk5mSFd3TDhmM054d1VMOC0wbENxMFRjQVVGZDlVaVFP?oc=5,AMD,,AMD stock news,119,17,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.128,-0.128,-0.128,negative,-0.05,negative,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""AMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 3}, {""text"": ""long weekend"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 27, ""end"": 39}, {""text"": ""$311 million"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 43, ""end"": 55}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 79, ""end"": 81}, {""text"": ""focus&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²"", ""label"": ""PRODUCT"", ""start"": 92, ""end"": 119}]","[{""text"": ""AMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9876213073730469, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 3}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.5048347115516663, ""start"": 79, ""end"": 81}, {""text"": ""S"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9437915682792664, ""start"": 113, ""end"": 114}]","[{""text"": ""AMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""long weekend"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""$311 million"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""focus&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²"", ""label"": ""PRODUCT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""S"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,4,0,0
2026-01-17 20:35:31,American Express (AXP) stock price rises ahead of rate-cap week — what investors watch next - TechStock²,American Express (AXP) stock price rises ahead of rate-cap week — what investors watch next&nbsp;&nbsp;TechStock²,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxOVkhvN2dBczM3UkZGYzdJSXBrUzJZNnJCcnhROWVWNWg2NGQwVnFpMmRoN3ZKaExTYndDd1ozRHotVVdKUGZkbEJKM2JzMDB6UDhRLXdjOUtKTXNiS1lPSEJEODBPbzA2Z09ibEZ2eWQ3SUphZTBSSF9fMlY3dWVkOU5udkV0ZXBaOER5N3BxX1pER3JqcF8tMnZQQk84TWRHUk4xdEFRMGZ5a004?oc=5,AXP,,AXP stock news,113,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""American Express"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 16}]","[{""text"": ""American Express"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9988423585891724, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 16}, {""text"": ""AXP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9046039581298828, ""start"": 18, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""S"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9199498891830444, ""start"": 107, ""end"": 108}]","[{""text"": ""American Express"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""American Express"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AXP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""S"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2026-01-17 15:00:21,The Goldman Sachs Group Has Lowered Expectations for American Tower (NYSE:AMT) Stock Price - MarketBeat,The Goldman Sachs Group Has Lowered Expectations for American Tower (NYSE:AMT) Stock Price&nbsp;&nbsp;MarketBeat,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2AFBVV95cUxONWRIbU8zWlEyNUZ0MnU4ak9XUHctWm52MHFRM2diQ3RBWlJDWTlWaS1SWDN2cnNTbURfaF9jYzBmSUgwelhNaFYteVN4eWo5OTZMWW1oTko1WE5zSGhHYmUxN090UWhCYzB3NENHOTVfbkp0VEE1enF5NlhvNG9BeGRpdk1fOGV5S2c5SS1nTUhnZFJDTWZBQXFLSDIzREtxLVRnb1BtN1hBOG1mQUpseWJxRndjSVNtSHRDREtnaTFZclZ4TWJsUWJsNGNjc1E2SmFQQnNXTTg?oc=5,AMT,,AMT stock news,112,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.128,-0.128,-0.128,negative,0.0,neutral,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""The Goldman Sachs Group"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 23}, {""text"": ""Lowered Expectations"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 28, ""end"": 48}, {""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 53, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 69, ""end"": 73}]","[{""text"": ""Goldman Sachs Group"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9991795420646667, ""start"": 4, ""end"": 23}, {""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.4841049909591675, ""start"": 53, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""B"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9390972256660461, ""start"": 108, ""end"": 109}]","[{""text"": ""The Goldman Sachs Group"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Lowered Expectations"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Goldman Sachs Group"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""B"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,6,0,1
2026-01-17 14:02:00,Accenture Stock (ACN) Opinions on AI Revenue Surge and Digital Identity Partnership - Quiver Quantitative,Accenture Stock (ACN) Opinions on AI Revenue Surge and Digital Identity Partnership&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxOODJyWGpEYzNEcTJ4aWdEeFY3QXl5d2xHdDFLSkxhaGh2ZHNnNDYweS13ZW5Td09tUDB3di03N0x2bFQxNG9ZSkpKdXFpeU9LcjJPYWpQWXc2bEhrdExNYWw3VlFCbVhodWFMUHlhcFhKdm9XQy1pMWV1TkdnU3pSQ2R2UjMtRlZza1F1ajh4MWNZOHNlTE50ZzhhQ0haZGJ4RThnX1R4YVp0TURfSEduUkhHMmJRb2t2aTRXeQ?oc=5,ACN,,ACN stock news,114,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""AI Revenue Surge"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 34, ""end"": 50}, {""text"": ""Digital Identity Partnership&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 55, ""end"": 114}]","[{""text"": ""AI Revenue Surge"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9665697813034058, ""start"": 34, ""end"": 50}, {""text"": ""Digital Identity Partnership"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8627017140388489, ""start"": 55, ""end"": 83}]","[{""text"": ""AI Revenue Surge"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Digital Identity Partnership&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AI Revenue Surge"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Digital Identity Partnership"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2026-01-17 11:44:57,Alibaba Group Holding Limited $BABA Shares Sold by Nations Financial Group Inc. IA ADV - MarketBeat,Alibaba Group Holding Limited $BABA Shares Sold by Nations Financial Group Inc. IA ADV&nbsp;&nbsp;MarketBeat,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi3gFBVV95cUxQY05zSVZYZXg4cFhLSFdVamdraDU0NTI3eHU1dWN1ZFF4VTh2ZXRTN3RXVUdBam1DTUlReGhmaHE2Y1hJbEtHODVHNDBZTHljZ1NON1V0blFGdGtsZmZpbmJoT0VBLTVOb0VDQ0ZTUUNZcmgtMXhMVW5ZQnpwZ29VaTgwSXVfVjJ1NlpGenBhaWZJWjV6cjJsLXFfc2FuX1lwVkdVX3RLbDVHb0hCSzZtbXNLUWpNZFA5TWp3UkFoSExJQVlDN0NtR1N5WkZSNGJIc25QY2RsVko5TkpNNkE?oc=5,BABA,,BABA stock news,108,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.0772,0.0772,0.0772,positive,-0.0357142857142857,neutral,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding Limited"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""BABA Shares Sold"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 31, ""end"": 47}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 51, ""end"": 79}, {""text"": ""IA"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 80, ""end"": 82}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding Limited"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9981849789619446, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9992995858192444, ""start"": 51, ""end"": 78}, {""text"": ""IA ADV"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8921256065368652, ""start"": 80, ""end"": 86}, {""text"": ""MarketBeat"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9519474506378174, ""start"": 98, ""end"": 108}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding Limited"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""BABA Shares Sold"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""IA"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding Limited"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Nations Financial Group Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""IA ADV"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""MarketBeat"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,6,1,1
2026-01-17 10:36:25,How to play BABA stock as Alibaba’s growth story gets a boost from the Chinese government - MSN,How to play BABA stock as Alibaba’s growth story gets a boost from the Chinese government&nbsp;&nbsp;MSN,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi1AFBVV95cUxPUTNXWUtHVy1WdmNlcV96MlZjTjR3MC1tbGs1VkIxMnZqclo2eVpUX0hMQTBaSWFMRHNHUTVKTzRYWG55MFppdXo1Wk1vb2IxeF9FX1VZc1JiWEJRNlZaLWlrNTh4NWVvQlVrSzhwTlA3VS1Pd2FIOVFnQVpDTzVweDJWRDgzQkN4ekdPRF94M3oybjFCQ3JTV0VJRl9jUUcxU2FVam1aM1hDWkgxbU56Rm8yczROcm1WQjAtNG5UUUE3ZFdPQ3RRZHhubS1RUzRtMzRUdA?oc=5,BABA,,BABA stock news,104,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.7717,0.7717,0.7717,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""Alibaba"", ""label"": ""NORP"", ""start"": 26, ""end"": 33}, {""text"": ""Chinese"", ""label"": ""NORP"", ""start"": 71, ""end"": 78}]","[{""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9973270893096924, ""start"": 12, ""end"": 16}, {""text"": ""Alibaba"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9990187287330627, ""start"": 26, ""end"": 33}, {""text"": ""Chinese"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.9997908473014832, ""start"": 71, ""end"": 78}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba"", ""label"": ""NORP"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Chinese"", ""label"": ""NORP"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Alibaba"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Chinese"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,2,0,0
2026-01-17 09:01:41,Abbott Laboratories (NYSE:ABT) Stands Out as a Dependable Dividend Stock for Income Investors - Chartmill,Abbott Laboratories (NYSE:ABT) Stands Out as a Dependable Dividend Stock for Income Investors&nbsp;&nbsp;Chartmill,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2AFBVV95cUxNWTl2Y1hyVWpjWkVWeDBoUkNhSXJJQUtPSnYzR1ZxcVcwY2g4X1pSZk9YX2lhZnEzY21lTkY4WElUMmlqZEY5RXlLbVR2QXVINk9MWVlxblNUZllpQWpPNlV1Q1gtWHIxby1wcWF1NVBzY3l1NmlkQlhsM1J4ejB4ZEVGS3MyeXJ1NWFlcXFJZXFwU2VUdW53S2JTOWMzcmUtcVJrS2tnLVp0ZlIyckZlcW40ZHFSUVo4NkRmdTFmcllNOXlNYW9rdWFqYzY1SHFEMjlCeDZWZDk?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,114,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-17,"[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 19}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 21, ""end"": 25}, {""text"": ""Dependable Dividend Stock for Income"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 47, ""end"": 83}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9992653727531433, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 19}, {""text"": ""Chartmill"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6192542314529419, ""start"": 105, ""end"": 114}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Dependable Dividend Stock for Income"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Chartmill"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,5,0,0
2026-01-16 22:00:00,Prediction: This Stock Will Join the $3 Trillion Club by the End of 2026. You're Going to Want to Buy It Now. - The Motley Fool,Prediction: This Stock Will Join the $3 Trillion Club by the End of 2026. You're Going to Want to Buy It Now.&nbsp;&nbsp;The Motley Fool,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxPVk5fOEpiUFJrdENxQlZELWVHTFhDLWNTdEthTmhtRXVPdlJ0eEUxTGw4Qjg4TmdITnVSRld6MDRkc2lZeVVqNWRNTjJCbDg2TmFneVhLcGZ5N1lLMUNyVm4yTmptVHp6eWFUTUEtS0lvRVVvbXZkdHlQMGRVZXlVWWZyRUhIeGI0OFphSDVaQXIweU00aHhhTA?oc=5,AVGO,,AVGO stock news,136,24,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.1027,-0.1027,-0.1027,negative,0.6,positive,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""$3 Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 37, ""end"": 53}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 68, ""end"": 72}]","[{""text"": ""Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7889629006385803, ""start"": 40, ""end"": 53}, {""text"": ""Motley Fool"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.7401909828186035, ""start"": 125, ""end"": 136}]","[{""text"": ""$3 Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Motley Fool"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,1,0,0
2026-01-16 21:21:00,"Lobbying Update: $60,000 of AMGEN INC. FKA HORIZON THERAPEUTICS USA INC. lobbying was just disclosed - Quiver Quantitative","Lobbying Update: $60,000 of AMGEN INC. FKA HORIZON THERAPEUTICS USA INC. lobbying was just disclosed&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi1gFBVV95cUxOeklOYkFwUnpZeU54akdUQk92MW9nMHpFSENKYU9yLTRtSkxzWlV0cHpOTkduYm9FcnBfcWpSUkxNdzAtQTRKNDU4a2ZQRnpmaHBBYW1QZ2dCTkVEYTZyeVBvQVNpUDlQYXowT19RbFhYM3NSbndFb0NlVVZDV1YxLTk5aDZSVXZFWEVBQ0RkWVhJWUQ4eWJRSndfNGJzRW5tRW1Cd0dsc0czRzQtVldjYXpJTHprVnN1anRSYy00QXdjanN5QWh5MW9jR1VPMV9Xb2VVdGVn?oc=5,AMGN,,AMGN stock news,131,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.1531,-0.1531,-0.1531,negative,0.0,neutral,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""Lobbying Update"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""60,000"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 18, ""end"": 24}, {""text"": ""AMGEN INC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 28, ""end"": 37}, {""text"": ""FKA HORIZON"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 39, ""end"": 50}, {""text"": ""THERAPEUTICS USA INC."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 51, ""end"": 72}]","[{""text"": ""FKA H"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8218682408332825, ""start"": 39, ""end"": 44}, {""text"": ""USA"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.9336401224136353, ""start"": 64, ""end"": 67}]","[{""text"": ""Lobbying Update"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""60,000"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AMGEN INC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""FKA HORIZON"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""THERAPEUTICS USA INC."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""FKA H"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""USA"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,4,1,1
2026-01-16 18:24:17,What Is Going On With AMD Stock On Friday? - Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ:AMD) - Benzinga,What Is Going On With AMD Stock On Friday? - Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ:AMD)&nbsp;&nbsp;Benzinga,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0AFBVV95cUxObnl4YThIUnFDNkVmNm9naDJEcHBfOFEzMjRKb0VpLTJZeHVrZ05RSThVVlBLNW5XYWFmQ2NoaXJPalZNdlBxTWFfRThva0E1RTh6RjVTYURUY3llSEowRkFJaERqbEVCbTJXcTRselJFVHJPVGVPOHVTZ0p6Q0J6UmRPWlVoR2Jqa0xSMmlYNnlqREc2S2dtNUlnbl91RWhYWXZYeE9ja0RJN1A0NmdrQkktTGdCOGVPVVJCWWdESThiU1FzbGd3alpfMDA1eF9i?oc=5,AMD,,AMD stock news,100,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.25,0.25,0.25,positive,0.4,positive,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""Friday"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 35, ""end"": 41}, {""text"": ""Advanced Micro Devices"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 45, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""NASDAQ"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 69, ""end"": 75}]","[{""text"": ""Advanced Micro Devices"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.900520920753479, ""start"": 45, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""Benzinga"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8481714725494385, ""start"": 92, ""end"": 100}]","[{""text"": ""Friday"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Advanced Micro Devices"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""NASDAQ"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Advanced Micro Devices"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Benzinga"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,4,0,0
2026-01-16 15:32:22,Wells Fargo Upgrades Broadcom Stock as New AI Catalysts Create Buying Opportunity - TIKR.com,Wells Fargo Upgrades Broadcom Stock as New AI Catalysts Create Buying Opportunity&nbsp;&nbsp;TIKR.com,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxOc0JOMlhLSlFDOEQ3Qm9NUDNtS3h0UEVsOGRsbUd1azFnQWFDSnZFYjJXN0trMzZQUkRVeS16RlFXREJWNkxHamM2Y21YSG9xR2lsUXFuQ053UFBoSmFDRS1ubjRHejhwdTFLN1JmM0g2UTRJNVZEd2RvOUFoam9aWGRZWS1sTmtyY05scmwtZw?oc=5,AVGO,,AVGO stock news,101,12,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.4767,0.4767,0.4767,positive,0.1363636363636363,positive,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""Wells Fargo Upgrades Broadcom Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 35}]","[{""text"": ""Wells Fargo"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9990568161010742, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 11}, {""text"": ""Broadcom"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9967555999755859, ""start"": 21, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""R"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7251699566841125, ""start"": 96, ""end"": 97}]","[{""text"": ""Wells Fargo Upgrades Broadcom Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Broadcom"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""R"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2026-01-16 14:00:06,Here is What to Know Beyond Why Alibaba Group Holding Limited (BABA) is a Trending Stock - Yahoo Finance,Here is What to Know Beyond Why Alibaba Group Holding Limited (BABA) is a Trending Stock&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxOV0lMbncxaGd2UHZhbVlLaV9fWUJmNWlvdWdHcDlrTW5ieExDUE1FZy1zZlh0eWthTXhpU1psTWc3bzVoMG9iQW1KU1F3RVV5dUo1eHZsNVFvUVhJZXV6Zk1NcG5wV0tWR2NZck9Cbmk0MlY0ckdVUmVZeU94MXc2RQ?oc=5,BABA,,BABA stock news,113,17,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.2263,-0.2263,-0.2263,negative,-0.0714285714285714,negative,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""a Trending Stock&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 72, ""end"": 113}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding Limited"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9990832805633545, ""start"": 32, ""end"": 61}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9953835606575012, ""start"": 63, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9944227933883667, ""start"": 100, ""end"": 113}]","[{""text"": ""a Trending Stock&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Alibaba Group Holding Limited"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2026-01-16 13:47:00,Fund Update: New $84.6M $ABT stock position opened by Compagnie Lombard Odier SCmA - Quiver Quantitative,Fund Update: New $84.6M $ABT stock position opened by Compagnie Lombard Odier SCmA&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxPelBwQnhHaDZvZjZIcXBld3h3SWtQR0JqRFE2bWZ0VENyaGRuV3g2blotQmVoeTl0NExpNHJFanFtc3ZmWGx2Q1J6MVBMOWRuSXN4Snl6RGRuUXJzM2lXN2pQeXFpclJxUmg2WVlVSDE5eHZDTkRod3BuNHhQREpOejhadXMwUlE0UGp6anp3VG1KQUY2NGh5QXlueWNEMVBCbExXTUNoa3hOSElHWGtaWUZTeW5jZ3BSX0ZqN1NB?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,113,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.1363636363636363,positive,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""84.6"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 18, ""end"": 22}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 25, ""end"": 28}]","[{""text"": ""New"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.8770809173583984, ""start"": 13, ""end"": 16}, {""text"": ""M"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.870577871799469, ""start"": 22, ""end"": 23}, {""text"": ""AB"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.5611557960510254, ""start"": 25, ""end"": 27}, {""text"": ""Compagnie Lombard Odier"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9887617826461792, ""start"": 54, ""end"": 77}, {""text"": ""Q"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6045840382575989, ""start"": 101, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""84.6"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""New"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""M"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AB"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Compagnie Lombard Odier"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Q"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,3,0,0
2026-01-16 13:41:00,Do Options Traders Know Something About APA Stock We Don't? - TradingView — Track All Markets,Do Options Traders Know Something About APA Stock We Don't?&nbsp;&nbsp;TradingView — Track All Markets,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxQcXltLVlJYlpXUXFCRkFOYkhQNE5qMGRpYXdDbi1zQ2RDZmhqN0I0WEI2eVlrNE54c0VmVXBXcEFGTkNZZHlCMFhoMTlRRmxocWp4ak1hbjZRY0FfZEg0c2dVcUJEdHR4dFhnSFFFZi1ZUVNRZHpoRExyNFpLU0hza3VEb08xOHpYZTVyX2FXTEtTeUNTa1ZmWDNkZDYxdXRxQzQtWURPckhEeEpzblkweGNJZE8?oc=5,APA,,APA stock news,102,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-16,[],"[{""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8121709823608398, ""start"": 40, ""end"": 43}, {""text"": ""Markets"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5341895818710327, ""start"": 95, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Markets"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",2,2,0,0
2026-01-16 11:43:35,TSMC Budget Boosts ASML Stock: Why Morgan Stanley Analysts Target 70% Gains by 2027 - TipRanks,TSMC Budget Boosts ASML Stock: Why Morgan Stanley Analysts Target 70% Gains by 2027&nbsp;&nbsp;TipRanks,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxQLTRZbjJjcEp4eV9XdEg3V29jUF9Oc043WTFjbGIyRWJsU0VZQ3RiU3pMazNXYVNjbVVtcXo2bkFTekp5WGh1WmVuZkJRdm9BTG8tQkNsZU50bUtkTDZIRlpfbldsWUFwclRmNE50T09GNFBhM2haUzR5Wm5ZVmwwbkk5anJGdy1JeEFMZlpJeENiRjdlSGhDM2RYSU0yMFBxMjhTZlRUaDJtdnpzLUlveA?oc=5,ASML,,ASML stock news,103,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.5719,0.5719,0.5719,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""TSMC Budget Boosts ASML Stock: Why Morgan Stanley Analysts Target"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 65}, {""text"": ""70%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""start"": 66, ""end"": 69}]","[{""text"": ""TSMC Budget"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9092503190040588, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 11}, {""text"": ""AS"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7840668559074402, ""start"": 19, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""ML"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.5652376413345337, ""start"": 21, ""end"": 23}, {""text"": ""Morgan Stanley"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9976366758346558, ""start"": 35, ""end"": 49}, {""text"": ""R"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9633237719535828, ""start"": 98, ""end"": 99}]","[{""text"": ""TSMC Budget Boosts ASML Stock: Why Morgan Stanley Analysts Target"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""70%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""TSMC Budget"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AS"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""ML"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Morgan Stanley"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""R"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,5,0,0
2026-01-16 10:09:54,Alibaba (BABA) Stock: Wall Street Backs AI Agent Strategy as Qwen App Gains Traction - CoinCentral,Alibaba (BABA) Stock: Wall Street Backs AI Agent Strategy as Qwen App Gains Traction&nbsp;&nbsp;CoinCentral,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxONGljMEtzWWIxenFXYVRSQ0QxQXM0Uy1XTi1CcUZrcWhMMjZWN29YblN3cnBiYmhJdEdyZzB1M3FYVWVGQWp0OWxpazNBbGJrVm1ERXJnTDRnTjJtTklFbTRmRTZWYVQ1TjdxeWJhd0hsbmItTWdMMldZdmh4VTVfbXNqUTBNRU80bmgxbkR6V3VadmpEWlltemhGS1JraXNWM1ZNNnh1VTYtUQ?oc=5,BABA,,BABA stock news,107,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.296,0.296,0.296,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""Qwen App Gains"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 61, ""end"": 75}]","[{""text"": ""Alibaba"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9394903182983398, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 7}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6292374730110168, ""start"": 9, ""end"": 13}, {""text"": ""Wall Street"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.9960911870002747, ""start"": 22, ""end"": 33}, {""text"": ""AI Agent"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.7599751949310303, ""start"": 40, ""end"": 48}, {""text"": ""Qwen A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7955937385559082, ""start"": 61, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""CoinCent"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8501403331756592, ""start"": 96, ""end"": 104}]","[{""text"": ""Qwen App Gains"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Alibaba"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BABA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wall Street"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AI Agent"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Qwen A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""CoinCent"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,4,1,1
2026-01-16 08:16:09,Absolute Software Co. (ABT.TO) (TSE:ABT) Stock Crosses Above Two Hundred Day Moving Average - Here's Why - MarketBeat,Absolute Software Co. (ABT.TO) (TSE:ABT) Stock Crosses Above Two Hundred Day Moving Average - Here's Why&nbsp;&nbsp;MarketBeat,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4gFBVV95cUxONmlKaGZYWGxlTS1RLS1KRkNMRnoxa2ZBQXJJcjJtaVI0TTZuVTk2UDlsWUNscXJCVXdJSTQ2N1B5VVZKXzhucXZCVmNyc0tSNGxfaHh3dzRKQ2w3bEVoNkhYZlFKUGNqRFplR2ZqM1ZFWEVHb0dxeF9jcF9SWTE0SDBDT1p2R0JqQjdxX1VzRzBXcjRhOWo0ZFhDNHhfemlZd0J5aUl2dVZ4TjhoNHJiWnJrSXRWY0tqM3p4SFo3UjE1dlJpT1BGV0s5VnRCeExfaTg5U2lkZG41dWRDV2M5UmNB?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,126,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0166666666666666,neutral,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""Absolute Software Co."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""ABT.TO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 23, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""TSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 32, ""end"": 35}]","[{""text"": ""Absolute Software Co."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9315754771232605, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9005625247955322, ""start"": 23, ""end"": 26}, {""text"": ""TO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7232280373573303, ""start"": 27, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""B"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8827370405197144, ""start"": 122, ""end"": 123}]","[{""text"": ""Absolute Software Co."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""ABT.TO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""TSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Absolute Software Co."", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""TO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""B"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,7,0,0
2026-01-16 06:29:29,BA stock is surging: Is Boeing finally figuring it out or is the market too optimistic? - investingLive,BA stock is surging: Is Boeing finally figuring it out or is the market too optimistic?&nbsp;&nbsp;investingLive,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxNMjJfdHdFbWNSRFk3aGJ0dlRBWkQyakttV1FCWEdRbGZ3RS1PMVhiZlRURUwyclE4ZE55S3I2bVdzbUVWTHh1c2wyY3RrV3dkMERZek9PTWJGMGY0X0I0Wm9aOU43R2FTbm0yNGN6UzZmY3R0VE1GWnU4Y3d0TTA1eEZGS0JIYzIwa1d2cDFaX0E0LWpTNkdicVZXc2c5MmhxRElkcTNuNTJJTEtVV0RQQjNWakIwNFV4TUtuQ3o0akJFd2FuQUFr0gHMAUFVX3lxTE9zMDNhajNQTk85SnBtSjdzWWg4bjlZd2xiYmVCVVY3QXdCeHBfdXdPLUM5Uklkc253TEFCZzVEbFM2TUpmRENPUlN0cnRFOTBtbmV0TF9kZzN3YjZOWng4Zk1Dem56MXRmbjdUTUZuZ0xsajQ3VjlCZFo3NVJtYlhYTDRvR0VlbFAtY3ZxOEhUSEloVlVSOThvYnBNOWJnWTF6TGZsY0FLZC02REhkYVBZazdrTnZJcjBobTRDT3RfdXJfbF9TdEQ3d29TZw?oc=5,BA,,BA stock news,112,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""NORP"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 2}, {""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 24, ""end"": 30}]","[{""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9984063506126404, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 2}, {""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9982144832611084, ""start"": 24, ""end"": 30}]","[{""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""NORP"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,3,0,0
2026-01-16 00:58:45,Is It Time To Reassess Alibaba (BABA) After Its 111% One Year Share Price Surge - simplywall.st,Is It Time To Reassess Alibaba (BABA) After Its 111% One Year Share Price Surge&nbsp;&nbsp;simplywall.st,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0gFBVV95cUxPVVJPcE5mQ1FwdWthQ05Ya1BKdnZPMjBhWGY4RGRxNS1CWHJORjJ0QkxZWXdXNGVfN01Vb3lKMkNyc0lYZ0dXTEtQSVVuVGtaNS1KM1FNekNRVktVWjRhcFJDUzFLcllNb1otbE1HX180SlVaYlRpUWdlTEYxVEdtX095TVEzQTJhaG5iU0dQdEFVWFRUN1pLaWdZSDZIcnNlZnFrYlJvZ0J4WVJSVGs4NVJPWEI4ZUg0cENrRVp3c0xFa3ZWazFNcEdIVGdPR0ljdVHSAdcBQVVfeXFMUG5wNE9LZnc3bkNJd25rbUZnWnMxVkU2VU1rVWlEeDU0YUF1eVROMjZGb0NxUkxhLTFBb3NXLWhIS08xUWFRQURwQXFISGZFWHZONG5SWFljcU1Ec2ZWdzg2ek1QU1JFRURCekhqTXhlaWY1aXBlSFN1NHA0VnVudFU4Zml6bFEtckR2R3NKNF94djh6SnB2THFEeEpKZWlGdjJCY1VLdkUtaGE3NGZVRjY1elZTbndQVVVEYk1QcGVPcC1FUWpGUDBNZTJhdG1nekVXX0NiZ0k?oc=5,BABA,,BABA stock news,104,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.296,0.296,0.296,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-16,"[{""text"": ""111%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""start"": 48, ""end"": 52}, {""text"": ""One Year"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 53, ""end"": 61}]","[{""text"": ""baba"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7767152786254883, ""start"": 26, ""end"": 30}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8366692066192627, ""start"": 32, ""end"": 34}]","[{""text"": ""111%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""One Year"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""baba"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,2,0,0
2026-01-15 22:53:00,Dow Gets A Boost From Revitalized AI Trade; AMD Stock Hits A Buy Point - Investor's Business Daily,Dow Gets A Boost From Revitalized AI Trade; AMD Stock Hits A Buy Point&nbsp;&nbsp;Investor's Business Daily,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxPTlpfYWdNTmRHYVo4R1NnMk1acWFiVEoyQktjbm00Q1FySy1RbTJuMTI3ZFhrekx5RUFUejh2V3JreUpVWks5SWplSXNGN1dSUUdZMTZMMlN3LUl2NWV2ZHhfODZoclRPWGJtUW9pcjNoakh3c2duOS10Z1R2NGtaWTFDclJHOU9LNlI1SXdRcw?oc=5,AMD,,AMD stock news,107,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.4019,0.4019,0.4019,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""AMD Stock Hits A Buy Point&nbsp;&nbsp;Investor's"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 44, ""end"": 92}, {""text"": ""Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 93, ""end"": 107}]","[{""text"": ""Dow"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.9500471949577332, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 3}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.797229528427124, ""start"": 34, ""end"": 36}, {""text"": ""AM"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5630987882614136, ""start"": 44, ""end"": 46}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9709482192993164, ""start"": 82, ""end"": 84}, {""text"": ""vestor ' s Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9185681343078613, ""start"": 84, ""end"": 107}]","[{""text"": ""AMD Stock Hits A Buy Point&nbsp;&nbsp;Investor's"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Dow"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AM"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""vestor ' s Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,5,0,0
2026-01-15 17:40:17,AMD Stock Jumps -- Wells Fargo Names It Top 2026 Pick - Yahoo Finance,"AMD Stock Jumps -- Wells Fargo Names It Top 2026 Pick&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo FinanceAMD, IBD Stock Of The Day, Jumps Into Buy Area On TSMC Results&nbsp;&nbsp;Investor's Business DailyAMD stock remains Wells Fargo’s top pick for 2026 on AI potential&nbsp;&nbsp;Investing.com",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE1FSXQ3NWNIbFlYaVlTVHE0cmxpa3lBcDZyTTV2VlMzMko2VHktUF8ySlU5SVBxYTBjS09TM29mX2swTU0zdjZmRk85TzAtdENBbldGV3ZReW5INHgxZUFSTjFPSjg0dHFSd0w3akl2N3NCNndCQnMwbFV4VmVVdw?oc=5,AMD,,AMD stock news,267,37,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.6808,0.6808,0.6808,positive,0.5,positive,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""AMD Stock Jumps"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo Names It"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 19, ""end"": 39}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 44, ""end"": 48}, {""text"": ""FinanceAMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 71, ""end"": 81}, {""text"": ""Business DailyAMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 163, ""end"": 180}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo’s"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 195, ""end"": 208}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 222, ""end"": 226}, {""text"": ""AI potential&nbsp;&nbsp;Investing.com"", ""label"": ""LAW"", ""start"": 230, ""end"": 267}]","[{""text"": ""AMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.729103147983551, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 3}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9989458322525024, ""start"": 19, ""end"": 30}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9867805242538452, ""start"": 65, ""end"": 78}, {""text"": ""IBD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7761716842651367, ""start"": 83, ""end"": 86}, {""text"": ""TSMC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9512739777565002, ""start"": 128, ""end"": 132}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.683383584022522, ""start"": 152, ""end"": 154}, {""text"": ""Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9833391904830933, ""start"": 172, ""end"": 177}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9987764358520508, ""start"": 195, ""end"": 206}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5897902250289917, ""start"": 254, ""end"": 256}]","[{""text"": ""AMD Stock Jumps"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo Names It"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""FinanceAMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Business DailyAMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo’s"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AI potential&nbsp;&nbsp;Investing.com"", ""label"": ""LAW"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AMD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""IBD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""TSMC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",17,14,0,0
2026-01-15 16:55:56,Dividend King Abbott Shows Why 52 Consecutive Increases Weren't Luck With Strong Cash Flow Coverage - 24/7 Wall St.,Dividend King Abbott Shows Why 52 Consecutive Increases Weren't Luck With Strong Cash Flow Coverage&nbsp;&nbsp;24/7 Wall St.,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2gFBVV95cUxNcThYVmFzVjloR3NHTS1EUy1YS0xqejczaERfMGd2Z3ZMZ1o3QXM1NDluQ1Z1eFM4MHVlem1zYm94OVo2dmlDckVFV0p5UmwwSDJ6YkV3RkNiQ1V0VUJTRXBzNDlZRTAxZG9fcklmTUhhby1RMUhXR0FDVDRSVlB5MzRpWmpSMWUxRWg2WkJZUTduWGxqeThGWmlBZ0lCcUVwX2tFb0swQWNwVXB6bFQtUi1ySE9UNlVqZTVOQzRsenBzY2tPRHIwRm95VjYwR1gxME53cWk2U3hkQQ?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,124,17,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.6348,-0.6348,-0.6348,negative,0.4333333333333333,positive,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""Abbott Shows"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 14, ""end"": 26}, {""text"": ""52"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 31, ""end"": 33}, {""text"": ""Consecutive Increases Weren't"", ""label"": ""EVENT"", ""start"": 34, ""end"": 63}, {""text"": ""Luck With Strong Cash Flow"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 64, ""end"": 90}]","[{""text"": ""King Abbott"", ""label"": ""PER"", ""score"": 0.9638381600379944, ""start"": 9, ""end"": 20}, {""text"": ""Wall St"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.9835337400436401, ""start"": 116, ""end"": 123}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Shows"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""52"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Consecutive Increases Weren't"", ""label"": ""EVENT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Luck With Strong Cash Flow"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""King Abbott"", ""label"": ""PER"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wall St"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",6,0,3,1
2026-01-15 16:00:00,CoreSite Chicago Data Center Campus Now Offers AWS Native 400G Direct Connect for Enhanced Cloud and AI Performance - Stock Titan,CoreSite Chicago Data Center Campus Now Offers AWS Native 400G Direct Connect for Enhanced Cloud and AI Performance&nbsp;&nbsp;Stock Titan,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNODJicU01Z1REN3J3WDNxaEZZVmhibmJGWXpHYzdxdkp0S2FkV2VvZ2tRSnlEYUtXZE1TcklURkdEeGMtcEdLSXpYMXBPSmhVU2w4NXN2a2NBd09qU0VfY2JTRzJKLUlGSmFHX0lIbGNLTG4waEtmcVc0MnhlS0NKMXJYSVR3X1FXbHAtWGNXenYyNC1IZW1PcUItRmR2WjZwUU5WVG5CTjVXbnB6ZE1SeXU0U3lfWjBN?oc=5,AMT,,AMT stock news,138,19,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0333333333333333,neutral,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""CoreSite Chicago Data Center Campus Now Offers AWS Native"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 57}, {""text"": ""G Direct Connect for Enhanced Cloud"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 61, ""end"": 96}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 101, ""end"": 103}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 133, ""end"": 138}]","[{""text"": ""Chicago Data Center"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8332899212837219, ""start"": 9, ""end"": 28}, {""text"": ""Stock Titan"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6127081513404846, ""start"": 127, ""end"": 138}]","[{""text"": ""CoreSite Chicago Data Center Campus Now Offers AWS Native"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""G Direct Connect for Enhanced Cloud"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Chicago Data Center"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Stock Titan"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",6,5,0,1
2026-01-15 15:49:58,"Amazon threatens 'drastic' action after Saks bankruptcy, says $475M stake is now worthless - CNBC","Amazon threatens 'drastic' action after Saks bankruptcy, says $475M stake is now worthless&nbsp;&nbsp;CNBC",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxQTVJZQjdQNDdoVTFab1lmMHJwenlUeHdQZVZtLWcybnFiZTdoX3E1bVl4Nm5EaHFaYWRCOEdPb3ZGVEJldng1ZGFNQV94czk4a2pEX181MFVQVDlRdXFMd1RDV2x5Y1VuX2VIcXBFSm1ZM2hmeEtHZlhtY0t5RlhrWU5RZ1pyZmVOV2NsNGZLRmlmaVRvMTJ1VGVB0gGfAUFVX3lxTFBQNjd4QWZhMURxcEtTWno0eG95WkpDM3dhRm5SLXlxa1pzS1ZDUTY1dE9LcXE3Sk43a2llNF9Sd2w2a3NCdXFmajFpTEdPSHp3bEhlN2MyNDMtbXdDMG40dE94dFF6SHJ2dklZbk9nS1RmUDJZa0tUVmFGeUZZaWpaS21jellZWkVJemxCRVVXaHZ5bXlxSW9JSm40c0c1TQ?oc=5,AMZN,,AMZN stock news,106,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.2263,-0.2263,-0.2263,negative,0.1,positive,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""Amazon"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""Saks"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 40, ""end"": 44}, {""text"": ""475"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 63, ""end"": 66}]","[{""text"": ""Amazon"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9988586902618408, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""Saks"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9950323104858398, ""start"": 40, ""end"": 44}, {""text"": ""CNBC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9187301397323608, ""start"": 102, ""end"": 106}]","[{""text"": ""Amazon"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Saks"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""475"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Amazon"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Saks"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""CNBC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",6,5,0,0
2026-01-15 14:08:00,Broadcom Inc. Stock (AVGO) Opinions on Recent Price Drop and Geopolitical Concerns - Quiver Quantitative,Broadcom Inc. Stock (AVGO) Opinions on Recent Price Drop and Geopolitical Concerns&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOcnJhdFV2Vm9ETlktM3dDNFdXcUNUT3AzaEw3RzQzTEl0ODlldUZ4NW51QU1aWUM2eUJNOUFlM1gzalQ3ZUE5bzlTX1hZbXU2b3ZnSnlQbjg3RlIxbTZTRjdnWEJUSERsWndrZ0NraGdyRnp0cHhKSFVHcFN5OUtfdHdJNkIxNXlrMUV6c0dsLVpLbnFqYW9lVW95TmVkejJOdUR6T0JMZ2d1ZjdoRTh6SE03T2JqTEVWR213?oc=5,AVGO,,AVGO stock news,113,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.2732,-0.2732,-0.2732,negative,0.0,neutral,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""Broadcom Inc. Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 19}, {""text"": ""AVGO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 21, ""end"": 25}, {""text"": ""Drop"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 52, ""end"": 56}]","[{""text"": ""Broadcom Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.998875617980957, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 12}]","[{""text"": ""Broadcom Inc. Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AVGO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Drop"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Broadcom Inc"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,3,1,0
2026-01-15 12:32:53,"Stocks making the biggest moves premarket: Taiwan Semiconductor, ASML, BlackRock and more - CNBC","Stocks making the biggest moves premarket: Taiwan Semiconductor, ASML, BlackRock and more&nbsp;&nbsp;CNBC",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxPUnVGZGpmZGdGWHhOQjV4aGdLSF9LbVpjWjdoa3BBUHN4WHNKejRHUmI2Q1pBSnVjVV9XNVI1ZkVxQ3JfZEhJRGhLVEFTWlhqbGpFZG1HT0k0aEhZbUFHZXcyc3pEU0hCeUJOb1VZYlpOdTBSR2R6R21aNGNkaDV4b002UzlUY0pXWEFldHNKVkRvaHhjZ2c?oc=5,ASML,,ASML stock news,105,12,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""Taiwan Semiconductor"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 43, ""end"": 63}, {""text"": ""ASML"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 65, ""end"": 69}, {""text"": ""BlackRock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 71, ""end"": 80}]","[{""text"": ""Taiwan Semiconductor"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9993966221809387, ""start"": 43, ""end"": 63}, {""text"": ""ASML"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9979453682899475, ""start"": 65, ""end"": 69}, {""text"": ""BlackRock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9973260760307312, ""start"": 71, ""end"": 80}, {""text"": ""CNBC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9744500517845154, ""start"": 101, ""end"": 105}]","[{""text"": ""Taiwan Semiconductor"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""ASML"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""BlackRock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Taiwan Semiconductor"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""ASML"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BlackRock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""CNBC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,7,0,0
2026-01-15 11:59:00,Accenture Named a Leader in Gartner  Magic Quadrant  for Digital Technology and Business Consulting Services - Stock Titan,Accenture Named a Leader in Gartner  Magic Quadrant  for Digital Technology and Business Consulting Services&nbsp;&nbsp;Stock Titan,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNb20zaVh5M280WnUwNlM4Ym1LQmJLTGFOSl9BU21aRkxubXdRMDRveVlIR2RrNF9KUy1qd0FMUmhzRGtneWtjUkNfaDFSM1VNZC0yMVp5ZF9neHVOY2FhZjh5Ml81QVFzT19pWlhOaGx4cTBFT3J0Wm5jX3VFRFp0QlEzamhyNkVkY2U0RmFZcnlzUEo1V0tUWE5ic0ZST2IwOE9xUGpxYkE3alBOZzNIa3pxNmJLdnY4eGM0?oc=5,ACN,,ACN stock news,131,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.25,positive,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""Accenture Named"", ""label"": ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Gartner®"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 28, ""end"": 36}, {""text"": ""Digital Technology and Business Consulting"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 57, ""end"": 99}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 126, ""end"": 131}]","[{""text"": ""Gartner® Magic Quadrant™"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.890556275844574, ""start"": 28, ""end"": 52}, {""text"": ""Digital Technology and Business Consulting Services"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9809209704399109, ""start"": 57, ""end"": 108}, {""text"": ""Stock Titan"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9492291808128357, ""start"": 120, ""end"": 131}]","[{""text"": ""Accenture Named"", ""label"": ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Gartner®"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Digital Technology and Business Consulting"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Gartner® Magic Quadrant™"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Digital Technology and Business Consulting Services"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Stock Titan"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,4,0,1
2026-01-15 09:35:43,Boeing (BA) Stock: Bernstein Names Aerospace Giant Top Pick for 2026 Recovery - CoinCentral,Boeing (BA) Stock: Bernstein Names Aerospace Giant Top Pick for 2026 Recovery&nbsp;&nbsp;CoinCentral,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxOUm5fSU9GQ2dnUTZMMEN4SEhad1pVa19WV2Z6TjVjSzBjd1U2TGxrbUZ2dmlfVS14ZzVNTDQ5bFZLX1BDU2F5clZXSlpBb2dMc0k3LXRmWnJKMGJBcjUyTE1sM0FzVVNrd0dBRWJsYXQ3TVJpTlVQTVpWeE93SlRGREtKcjZTa3BJYUZEb2d0ei1qY2pnSnQ3dTV2bzllQnUx?oc=5,BA,,BA stock news,100,12,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.2023,0.2023,0.2023,positive,0.25,positive,2026-01-15,"[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""Bernstein Names Aerospace Giant Top Pick"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 19, ""end"": 59}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 64, ""end"": 68}]","[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.99718177318573, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8608418703079224, ""start"": 8, ""end"": 10}, {""text"": ""Bernstein Names Aerospace"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9820727705955505, ""start"": 19, ""end"": 44}, {""text"": ""CoinCent"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8430952429771423, ""start"": 89, ""end"": 97}]","[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Bernstein Names Aerospace Giant Top Pick"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Bernstein Names Aerospace"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""CoinCent"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,6,0,0
2026-01-14 21:22:00,"Bank of America, Wells Fargo Slip, Citi Pops On Bank Earnings Day 2 - Investor's Business Daily","Bank of America, Wells Fargo Slip, Citi Pops On Bank Earnings Day 2&nbsp;&nbsp;Investor's Business Daily",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxPVV8wSDF0R1p1Uzl1T2xSZ0ljRS1pekk3eXRiQTh1TUNyVXpzLVdubUFCdlhNbGRJMmgyR2JHRC0zbTVkLXgwWjVvT2tZbW5lQWNqX3VNWDAtd0Z6QXFOTFNzYzVXWVdTNGg3UG43R3E3SWctNms5TWFqLTE5ci1pUXkyY1MtbWxLbmoySUc1aVI0Q2dXZENDYXNTOWhqdw?oc=5,BAC,,BAC stock news,104,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.25,0.25,0.25,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo Slip"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 17, ""end"": 33}, {""text"": ""Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 90, ""end"": 104}]","[{""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.999323844909668, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo Slip"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9992512464523315, ""start"": 17, ""end"": 33}, {""text"": ""Citi Pops On Bank"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9451368451118469, ""start"": 35, ""end"": 52}, {""text"": ""Day"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.9718347191810608, ""start"": 62, ""end"": 65}, {""text"": ""Investor ' s Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9088788032531738, ""start"": 79, ""end"": 104}]","[{""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo Slip"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wells Fargo Slip"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Citi Pops On Bank"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Day"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Investor ' s Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,7,0,0
2026-01-14 18:22:30,BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print – Guides For Mid-Single Digit NII Growth In FY26 - Stocktwits,BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print – Guides For Mid-Single Digit NII Growth In FY26&nbsp;&nbsp;Stocktwits,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxQODNUc0JnaW5TNTFjZmFaNWdsOWwzdl9YRHpxbVllT0V6WkpZMmZhXzJYaWtNVWdybUItTFFJeEZnTGxiSTR1bVlGTlJjUUJYM0oySGptUGM2Q2tUR0V4Qko2QzBtYldyeHdIdXhJRjdyNnZTTDJ0Rnd6aGpjTXRoQlQ3SFJnc2hKUHFhb0lhazM1SXNzRF9TRVlTdms?oc=5,BAC,,BAC stock news,106,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.6124,0.6124,0.6124,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 35}]","[{""text"": ""N"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.835822582244873, ""start"": 66, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7968324422836304, ""start"": 96, ""end"": 101}]","[{""text"": ""BAC Stock Gains On Bullish Q4 Print"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""N"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",3,2,0,0
2026-01-14 17:47:36,AVGO Stock Dives as Insider Selling and China Risks Revive Broadcom Valuation Fears - FXLeaders,AVGO Stock Dives as Insider Selling and China Risks Revive Broadcom Valuation Fears&nbsp;&nbsp;FXLeaders,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixAFBVV95cUxNLWF2U0VVRnM4SE5pT2ZwYXNmOG1BUmFJZXg1akFucE5aR2ZKaEZZNVQyWWYtNGlYYVlhaHFTN2YwSUxPSThxYnQ4YVFJbjV1V0EwRU9ialNYTDhYNW5oZlNVbjZYQkJBNnpXa2xZNlppUnZxXzl5RE9VakRFekdEN2h4SHBEcGRPZDRrSS1mQjdTWGlkeXpYd2Jac29oWmFSNWR4ekZURUlKbkpwNU5pSHZ3TWJMV2FFR0dIa0kwN0JFRVpp?oc=5,AVGO,,AVGO stock news,104,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.0772,0.0772,0.0772,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""AVGO Stock Dives"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 16}, {""text"": ""China Risks Revive Broadcom Valuation"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 40, ""end"": 77}]","[{""text"": ""A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9635639786720276, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 1}, {""text"": ""VGO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9224900603294373, ""start"": 1, ""end"": 4}, {""text"": ""com"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.735940158367157, ""start"": 64, ""end"": 67}, {""text"": ""FXL"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6133661270141602, ""start"": 95, ""end"": 98}]","[{""text"": ""AVGO Stock Dives"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""China Risks Revive Broadcom Valuation"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""VGO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""com"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""FXL"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",6,6,0,0
2026-01-14 17:21:08,Broadcom CEO Hock Tan Just Sold $24 Million Worth of AVGO Stock. Should You Dump Shares Too? - Barchart.com,Broadcom CEO Hock Tan Just Sold $24 Million Worth of AVGO Stock. Should You Dump Shares Too?&nbsp;&nbsp;Barchart.com,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizwFBVV95cUxQWGFJWmVFT2V0bm0zOUZYMGtKN3FFc0xXWUp1ZXNDSTVGVGNTMFJoUmhhUDVlbV90ZDJ6SGJHYzU1TWNhTGJZcm8wR2JRbG54TU1sWnBQa1RhbFN4dWg0alJEZ1NhaHRIazdzY0xqV2p4SnVlVExGWkY5S1ZGbUJ6NTQtd1dTelpXWWpOSXJ1UFlDZXB5NWZNam8zR0FtRXFIWnVzWHZIQk9sd01xZ2VYdU82eEdVaGJUa2FYcUpkU3FUd3ltcGs5aGZ4TEx3WHM?oc=5,AVGO,,AVGO stock news,116,17,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.128,0.128,0.128,positive,0.3,positive,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""Hock Tan"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 13, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""$24 Million"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 32, ""end"": 43}, {""text"": ""AVGO Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 53, ""end"": 63}]","[{""text"": ""Broadcom"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9973959922790527, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 8}, {""text"": ""Ho"", ""label"": ""PER"", ""score"": 0.9995468258857727, ""start"": 13, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""ck Tan"", ""label"": ""PER"", ""score"": 0.755711019039154, ""start"": 15, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9473863840103149, ""start"": 53, ""end"": 54}, {""text"": ""VG"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6674816012382507, ""start"": 54, ""end"": 56}, {""text"": ""Barchart. com"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8954590559005737, ""start"": 104, ""end"": 116}]","[{""text"": ""Hock Tan"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""$24 Million"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AVGO Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Broadcom"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Ho"", ""label"": ""PER"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""ck Tan"", ""label"": ""PER"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""VG"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Barchart. com"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",9,5,3,0
2026-01-14 15:38:51,BAC stock today falls despite Bank of America beating Q4 earnings estimates: What investors are worried ab - The Economic Times,BAC stock today falls despite Bank of America beating Q4 earnings estimates: What investors are worried ab&nbsp;&nbsp;The Economic Times,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgJBVV95cUxOazBwRGlYN0h3ZFlyYy1iMUlCS0syRmdyQ0hvYzNpaUJOaFBENUFVN0FQVG96aHZzaWRYb0poQWlVSlBJRUgyY0lZUENaN3pocHRZT1VoRV9FYzlza2NWMkxKVEtrUk9DMFN3VUQ2ZEUwYzVhMG9YaEJxQWx3UU5PNWNxRnNEdzVoeTRwTWFjb245YWZIMlBsdXBtRE1fREJhSXQwVDBhbVhxVDZLRG0zQ2tzZGVHYmxsRC1USl9FMm4yVExkUHVzVlZXQWdzVTliZ1lCZ2xKdFZwQ0tkRHN2REVYemQ1aHNGUXhMRTZ4cUhtZWE4Q3FySXJ3eEdnY1lQQmFGUnVsdHEtcVBReFhKYkx30gGXAkFVX3lxTE5laVlLUWdCdVZ3V0lsWFpkaHhGNTR3NURDaDRwMmlzdTZRS19LMDdKYVlFNkw1dzZMczZ0T2tNLXBGN1RxMXZmZXFhVXBteHRQalhvaUo5d1dvSVJLS2FtaVhMNTNHOWlZdEVwV0VHazdzbXV3aW5MMGQtYWdwdVFwbTFiT0w2YzF5N0xST0VYZFBSNHJzdWpZWUZaWUtGT2c1RGphWEprOFY2YTdnZ09BVUxocGNXakJRQUJpQzNlUUUzeHIwcWhuYlhlMnplZDl6eHJPOTNlTWxncWx2cnIwRWhTRnlHT3JaUURSX3hJVFN2SllpQ2hNYnBpTWlUZU96M195cVBLN2ZNakFmWlBwVmtrVWdSdw?oc=5,BAC,,BAC stock news,136,19,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.6369,-0.6369,-0.6369,negative,0.2,positive,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""BAC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 3}, {""text"": ""today"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 10, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 30, ""end"": 45}, {""text"": ""ab&nbsp;&nbsp;The Economic Times"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 104, ""end"": 136}]","[{""text"": ""BAC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9967155456542969, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 3}, {""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9993719458580017, ""start"": 30, ""end"": 45}, {""text"": ""The Economic Times"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9589545130729675, ""start"": 118, ""end"": 136}]","[{""text"": ""BAC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""today"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""ab&nbsp;&nbsp;The Economic Times"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""BAC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""The Economic Times"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,6,0,0
2026-01-14 14:00:03,Accenture PLC (ACN) is Attracting Investor Attention: Here is What You Should Know - Yahoo Finance,Accenture PLC (ACN) is Attracting Investor Attention: Here is What You Should Know&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPelVEMzRHbGlHaXg3QUVYT29FejhtMzNEd3luS0QtVEVGcW43UWJZd2VZeUZVM25EX0pEUUxINHQ4aXFYSG1TNVJNZnhfZ005OVlpaVVJb1liN1JmMTNVNkdERzhaS2FJLWtmNmtRdGJQeUU5ODhSRWN0UzE0dmVUSnprSmxWU1lweHNF?oc=5,ACN,,ACN stock news,107,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.4767,0.4767,0.4767,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""Accenture PLC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 13}, {""text"": ""ACN"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 15, ""end"": 18}]","[{""text"": ""PLC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9559171199798584, ""start"": 10, ""end"": 13}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9962101578712463, ""start"": 94, ""end"": 107}]","[{""text"": ""Accenture PLC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""ACN"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""PLC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2026-01-14 12:45:18,Broadcom (NASDAQ: AVGO) Stock Price Prediction and Forecast 2026-2030 (Jan 2026) - 24/7 Wall St.,Broadcom (NASDAQ: AVGO) Stock Price Prediction and Forecast 2026-2030 (Jan 2026)&nbsp;&nbsp;24/7 Wall St.,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxNZEF2R2VfRmVUSG9QMmh0czhqYlpKb1VjWnE1Smc3c09HcDloLUYxUXlhVzFWYXYxUVEyYXNxLXFZRDJ1M1haVGdMakFRQ3NKZE02WUk5UDluMV9EenZGb184QklZRHhDWllsM3dsZFROS2tsdUR3cWVsT1NnbUF6T3dJdVFpZVJfenRfOUl0QTdQLU9RdUpWVVM2MmlJdw?oc=5,AVGO,,AVGO stock news,105,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""AVGO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 18, ""end"": 22}]","[{""text"": ""Broadcom"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9840444326400757, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 8}, {""text"": ""Wall St"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.9847061634063721, ""start"": 97, ""end"": 104}]","[{""text"": ""AVGO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Broadcom"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wall St"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",3,2,0,1
2026-01-14 12:30:37,Amazon Stock (NASDAQ: AMZN) Price Prediction and Forecast 2026-2030 for January 14 - 24/7 Wall St.,Amazon Stock (NASDAQ: AMZN) Price Prediction and Forecast 2026-2030 for January 14&nbsp;&nbsp;24/7 Wall St.,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxNQ3MwcC1WVkc1bENwcS1obkZ2dGRLUnhPUkpkTHRoZlA1eWpkeXBUb09Jb3Jha2ZuOExBUEtPSGxfOGhNSVVWOTZfcDZwZ0ctSGY1QzdtVzJSeWZneUgzQ0dOV1J4S0ZzakhqVWM3OUxIazVPU1I3UDlQdXZROU9tQmIwM2pPRlVjR1N5TUROa0lRamF3UlE?oc=5,AMZN,,AMZN stock news,107,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.1779,0.1779,0.1779,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""Amazon Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 12}, {""text"": ""January 14&nbsp;&nbsp;24/7"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 72, ""end"": 98}]","[{""text"": ""Amazon"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8528382182121277, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""Wall St"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.9932278394699097, ""start"": 99, ""end"": 106}]","[{""text"": ""Amazon Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""January 14&nbsp;&nbsp;24/7"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Amazon"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wall St"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,2,0,1
2026-01-14 11:15:01,"Bank of America tops estimates on better-than-expected net interest income, equities trading - CNBC","Bank of America tops estimates on better-than-expected net interest income, equities trading&nbsp;&nbsp;CNBC",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE5KSFFjNUtvRV9CM0l4QWlhLUhIMW8wRlg5TEVVOWlmaERHaUF1a2xOaGJYby1hem9aTk1uTEwwN1E5Z1d3M0hhQ1dpOHR1RzI3VWMxLVhQdEdMai1uSkh2TkxrYXAwa3EyVlU2MlB2emI4YkRuWkoxd1dOdGo0d9IBgwFBVV95cUxNckZ4aWxaaC02V1FIelBKa2FkVDBUUnlPckx3MFhvODd5bFAtc05EVWRXSTU3UTNza3M3djdscWJrYlhlVG4yaXBkQVJXaFN5S1dSSFkyVENCY2JSNGlSeEhWUzFQS09ZeWR4a1Y4SFQzajNaU2Y4eVRqZ3ZrY0tyeV95WQ?oc=5,BAC,,BAC stock news,108,12,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.743,0.743,0.743,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}]","[{""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9993283152580261, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""CNBC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9643941521644592, ""start"": 104, ""end"": 108}]","[{""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Bank of America"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""CNBC"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",3,3,0,0
2026-01-14 08:02:00,"This Unstoppable Stock Has 4 Catalysts to Fuel Its Membership in the $5 Trillion Club in 2026, According to 1 Wall Street Analyst. - The Motley Fool","This Unstoppable Stock Has 4 Catalysts to Fuel Its Membership in the $5 Trillion Club in 2026, According to 1 Wall Street Analyst.&nbsp;&nbsp;The Motley Fool",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxPUjdkT2laVks2S2RVMmdBNy1jQWR0Z0F0dlJHSjFSdFp0TXk2dVozYjZpZDhPWEdXVlpvMVNMRVZSb3F3MnU3ci1CaGcxRWktbnRGR0tGeGFkcFEzMm90QkdPMWhRWVp1bUx2LWw1OWk0QjFWMU9uYzM3NVd2WldDSkJObmotd0JGdEdBSVdvblFBcXZGNTJRbQ?oc=5,AAPL,,AAPL stock news,157,25,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.5719,-0.5719,-0.5719,negative,0.6,positive,2026-01-14,"[{""text"": ""4"", ""label"": ""CARDINAL"", ""start"": 27, ""end"": 28}, {""text"": ""$5 Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 69, ""end"": 85}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 89, ""end"": 93}, {""text"": ""1"", ""label"": ""CARDINAL"", ""start"": 108, ""end"": 109}]","[{""text"": ""Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9463529586791992, ""start"": 72, ""end"": 85}, {""text"": ""Wall Street"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""score"": 0.9563729763031006, ""start"": 110, ""end"": 121}, {""text"": ""Motley"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.5916664004325867, ""start"": 146, ""end"": 152}, {""text"": ""Fool"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5883258581161499, ""start"": 153, ""end"": 157}]","[{""text"": ""4"", ""label"": ""CARDINAL"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""$5 Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""1"", ""label"": ""CARDINAL"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Trillion Club"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Wall Street"", ""label"": ""LOC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Motley"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Fool"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,2,0,1
2026-01-13 22:10:08,AI Could Spell Trouble for Software. These Experts Say to Avoid One Stock In Particular - Investopedia,AI Could Spell Trouble for Software. These Experts Say to Avoid One Stock In Particular&nbsp;&nbsp;Investopedia,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiyAFBVV95cUxPSUFXVGp3c2VaSUxXV211UE5LdnBHUDRRNEZhazh4TFBOUWNUdTkyenRndWxReFNkMmVNTHBFcWNXQ21EcjhndGpUbW82WkRadXBEWlMxYjFPUlRLc0d6Rkg1c25Oc3pJelpneDREeFhtS1dWZHhjTGFKV0p3MmlkdXBTcDVJWnRLVjBFUFc2eWRRQWlHMmx0MGFfZXV3dml5MWFDamhJWVZyN1ZZdXJuYUZmMGhFcjBPRTl6YlgwZG9jZk5McW42OQ?oc=5,ADBE,,ADBE stock news,111,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.5994,-0.5994,-0.5994,negative,-0.2,negative,2026-01-13,"[{""text"": ""AI Could Spell Trouble for Software"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 35}, {""text"": ""Avoid One Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 58, ""end"": 73}]","[{""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7096765637397766, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 2}, {""text"": ""Investopedia"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8274959921836853, ""start"": 99, ""end"": 111}]","[{""text"": ""AI Could Spell Trouble for Software"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Avoid One Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AI"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Investopedia"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2026-01-13 19:03:00,Fund Update: New $26.2M $AVB stock position opened by FORT WASHINGTON INVESTMENT ADVISORS INC |OH| - Quiver Quantitative,Fund Update: New $26.2M $AVB stock position opened by FORT WASHINGTON INVESTMENT ADVISORS INC |OH|&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQUW1vWkVtRm1FX3BiMEg0V09YNjJyRkkxZkR2dmFGLTVQS1lfN1EwamtySjl1MzNoaVVyLWhVcTlTT1VBNUl5Y3hxaDYtVzAya0VKaENwZ1lMRWptTUVVLWlPRmtQUHB2NFFvTzlRMnJnTWdHUEM5eUs3T1NRREFraFJ2UVhUdXNfeUt2eDE1S1FzN0tkd2Z6RTc3WXVpZVlHaHdWWVJBVjdNWTh5eDNrR1kyZmhmbTJxb1JPVC1aRUJWZmljUXRQZGRQeW9hbG90b0tiZ2xBOXQ?oc=5,AVB,,AVB stock news,129,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.1363636363636363,positive,2026-01-13,"[{""text"": ""$26.2M $"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 17, ""end"": 25}, {""text"": ""AVB"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 25, ""end"": 28}, {""text"": ""FORT WASHINGTON INVESTMENT ADVISORS INC |OH|&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 54, ""end"": 129}]","[{""text"": ""TO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.6872243285179138, ""start"": 66, ""end"": 68}]","[{""text"": ""$26.2M $"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AVB"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""FORT WASHINGTON INVESTMENT ADVISORS INC |OH|&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""TO"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,3,0,0
2026-01-13 16:20:04,Adobe Stock Drops as The Most Pessimistic Analyst Forecast Since 2013 Hits ADBE Shares - TipRanks,Adobe Stock Drops as The Most Pessimistic Analyst Forecast Since 2013 Hits ADBE Shares&nbsp;&nbsp;TipRanks,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxQN052RzBlbzBSRm5GZEZsSzhOWFZWRWc0V2RQc191ZVNNNkRTS3ZOVFBkS2VqZ3dfQ05vSjhFNFR5QjhvTEZWcXFYT2ppTy1fX3RDTUpTZ0diN3hLSTFELXd6YW5vbG1ab3BZYW0yTmktbnltb2p3VXZRa3d4NVVyeXZvcjJpRkJZdlBEcWo5NzlDS2VUUzZIa0dUb3RsU0d4aC00QTJ6MUJxa3NkWU1rN2IyMTNjT0k?oc=5,ADBE,,ADBE stock news,106,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.4201,-0.4201,-0.4201,negative,0.5,positive,2026-01-13,"[{""text"": ""2013"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 65, ""end"": 69}]","[{""text"": ""Adobe Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7207072377204895, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 11}, {""text"": ""AD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9327614307403564, ""start"": 75, ""end"": 77}, {""text"": ""R"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.7144364714622498, ""start"": 101, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""2013"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Adobe Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AD"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""R"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,3,0,0
2026-01-09 08:00:00,Boeing stock forecast 2026: Here’s why BA shares will soar - TradingView — Track All Markets,Boeing stock forecast 2026: Here’s why BA shares will soar&nbsp;&nbsp;TradingView — Track All Markets,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxNTHpvUkNkcjcwWnJEVjB0bXVLLTJLSGp6OHp0TnpjdnpLZTV1NFd5X2FzT1FZYlI0MDRFNXlRNmdzOHRiMEZPOXlEU29aX3ZXTnBWMG5NYWU5dTcxNnBRZGhMTVJ2RjBNZDlSOVltc3o3Vm1SMlAyODFXcWQ1R2pYN2VRdEFYZHAxY1ZNd254ME84V2lWYjRtdjF6c2lNWkd2dVV4RlEyZGN5UDFNaXdZNGRFN0k?oc=5,BA,,BA stock news,101,14,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.296,0.296,0.296,positive,0.0,neutral,2026-01-09,"[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 22, ""end"": 26}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 39, ""end"": 41}, {""text"": ""soar&nbsp;&nbsp;TradingView"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 54, ""end"": 81}]","[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9986608028411865, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9988197684288025, ""start"": 39, ""end"": 41}, {""text"": ""All"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5607580542564392, ""start"": 90, ""end"": 93}, {""text"": ""Markets"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.4950222373008728, ""start"": 94, ""end"": 101}]","[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""2026"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""soar&nbsp;&nbsp;TradingView"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""BA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""All"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Markets"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,6,0,0
2026-01-08 08:00:00,"Markets News, Dec. 8, 2025: Major Stock Indexes Close Mixed; Dow Advances; Data-Storage Shares Drag Nasdaq - Investopedia","Markets News, Dec. 8, 2025: Major Stock Indexes Close Mixed; Dow Advances; Data-Storage Shares Drag Nasdaq&nbsp;&nbsp;Investopedia",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMib0FVX3lxTE1ONEhoNHJSa3lxQ0tMaXV4eXhvT2dCN2NIVVZRUDM0T0FYRXVCUjFuUElsdFE4am5DaWpxQnduN3BkQlUtYWtGa3NtSkYwTHJhWmtxeEdDZ3A1Q3pxc1RIVUVrZXJWY1dmNFQwdVNOaw?oc=5,APA,,APA stock news,130,16,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.0772,0.0772,0.0772,positive,-0.0125,neutral,2026-01-08,"[{""text"": ""Markets News"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 12}, {""text"": ""Dec. 8, 2025"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 14, ""end"": 26}, {""text"": ""Dow Advances"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 61, ""end"": 73}, {""text"": ""Data-Storage"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 75, ""end"": 87}]","[{""text"": ""Markets News"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9769676923751831, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 12}, {""text"": ""Major Stock Index"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.9425138831138611, ""start"": 28, ""end"": 45}, {""text"": ""Dow Advances"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.9776504039764404, ""start"": 61, ""end"": 73}, {""text"": ""Na"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""score"": 0.6802351474761963, ""start"": 100, ""end"": 102}, {""text"": ""Investopedia"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9905027151107788, ""start"": 118, ""end"": 130}]","[{""text"": ""Markets News"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Dec. 8, 2025"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Dow Advances"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Data-Storage"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Markets News"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Major Stock Index"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Dow Advances"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Na"", ""label"": ""MISC"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Investopedia"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",9,5,0,0
2026-01-07 21:37:00,Boeing '26 Gets Strong Start As Airline Posts Largest Order Ever - Investor's Business Daily,Boeing '26 Gets Strong Start As Airline Posts Largest Order Ever&nbsp;&nbsp;Investor's Business Daily,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxNZTRxODVPYm8wOG9uVFNQTHJldTk0cjE0Wkg0VUdFeXN6NzViTTQ5aVIxQ3MtZWFic2FiQWVKZGxIcjZfZWdZRVFSOS1pYjBsSkhoTk8tNFN0NDJQekVTMkNTRGJLNmRvUnZFVXFXSVh0X1p6Vm0tcHBPWFlZV2oyZ3ctN0dHLUdKQXBZY1Mzd3lzN0ZoWk10bml2TUM2dmgyOWc?oc=5,BA,,BA stock news,101,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.5106,0.5106,0.5106,positive,0.2166666666666666,positive,2026-01-07,"[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 6}, {""text"": ""26"", ""label"": ""CARDINAL"", ""start"": 8, ""end"": 10}, {""text"": ""Gets"", ""label"": ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""start"": 11, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 87, ""end"": 101}]","[{""text"": ""Boeing ' 26"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9550175666809082, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 10}, {""text"": ""Airline"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8876314759254456, ""start"": 32, ""end"": 39}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9636836647987366, ""start"": 76, ""end"": 78}, {""text"": ""vestor ' s Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8863039612770081, ""start"": 78, ""end"": 101}]","[{""text"": ""Boeing"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""26"", ""label"": ""CARDINAL"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Gets"", ""label"": ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Boeing ' 26"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Airline"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""In"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""vestor ' s Business Daily"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,6,0,0
2025-12-31 08:00:00,Here is What to Know Beyond Why Abbott Laboratories (ABT) is a Trending Stock - Yahoo Finance,Here is What to Know Beyond Why Abbott Laboratories (ABT) is a Trending Stock&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxORUwzODRyM2dzaUJqNHVpRWxXR1oyd2pVcEhHOGFPVlB4czRLQm1qeGZhdnJtUVVSX25acERTWU5iaXpjUzA4UVF6SEFla3pabWlfTGl0S29nYzNqa1g5Z3dySVZnTkt3Rm8xWFpKWHM5N1dLc2tGY1JSX2g0RW5VRTRzRG9URjdx?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,102,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2025-12-31,"[{""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 53, ""end"": 56}, {""text"": ""a Trending Stock&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 61, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9982092380523682, ""start"": 32, ""end"": 51}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9909117221832275, ""start"": 53, ""end"": 56}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.977424144744873, ""start"": 89, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""a Trending Stock&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""ABT"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,5,0,0
2025-12-27 08:00:00,Is Weakness In Abbott Laboratories (NYSE:ABT) Stock A Sign That The Market Could be Wrong Given Its Strong Financial Prospects? - Yahoo Finance,Is Weakness In Abbott Laboratories (NYSE:ABT) Stock A Sign That The Market Could be Wrong Given Its Strong Financial Prospects?&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOSEE1MThkcHRSR1luWnZPMzc3V0lUMlhwa1QyZUNPelgyOGJhSGZSdVJwSFdHek8wS2NKM2F2S0ZfVWlFbklEWXRTbUdPYjQ2N01XSWRhU2tCcm9wREhfbWJHNnNOQnZtaUZqQjlTWVdQRGtCbEJna3M3M0hxY1BQSjBEN21VMUstSGcw?oc=5,ABT,,ABT stock news,152,21,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,negative,0.3818,-0.3818,-0.3818,negative,-0.0222222222222222,neutral,2025-12-27,"[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 15, ""end"": 34}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 36, ""end"": 40}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9622575044631958, ""start"": 15, ""end"": 34}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9946107864379883, ""start"": 139, ""end"": 152}]","[{""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Abbott Laboratories"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2025-12-27 08:00:00,American Electric Power Stock (AEP) Opinions on Recent Performance and Growth Plans - Quiver Quantitative,American Electric Power Stock (AEP) Opinions on Recent Performance and Growth Plans&nbsp;&nbsp;Quiver Quantitative,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxNVW5LYm80ZUF3TWt3NEZjT3pXaEZYX3ZuRlNwN29nNzBVR3QzM2d5U2JPN2U5WUhyQXFyM040MVBrLXdHZzBqUHdraGRfTlBxNm9qSEwtZ0NBdFdLWHVDRlpuem5DLUppcUlNMUlsTnZlckFWWU5iTHdIMFBoMWpsa2dfVXY4Qy1ndUltcVEzVXlQb28zZ3hQMXBxaVkzeXBydkp2RG5YWEdiVTIyVE84N0dTalVVdkdEOEJVMQ?oc=5,AEP,,AEP stock news,114,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.3818,0.3818,0.3818,positive,0.0,neutral,2025-12-27,"[{""text"": ""American Electric Power Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 29}]","[{""text"": ""American Electric Power Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9501128196716309, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8119012713432312, ""start"": 31, ""end"": 32}, {""text"": ""EP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.4055576026439667, ""start"": 32, ""end"": 34}]","[{""text"": ""American Electric Power Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""American Electric Power Stock"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""A"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""EP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",4,4,0,0
2025-12-11 08:00:00,AvalonBay Communities (AVB): Valuation Check After $340 Million Asset Sales and New Investor Presentation - Yahoo Finance,AvalonBay Communities (AVB): Valuation Check After $340 Million Asset Sales and New Investor Presentation&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikAFBVV95cUxQNlFfMFZRa08xSWFiRWM2SmgyZFF0dm5lM1VmVldUR09BQ1ZkRlVQMmxid2tyV1lMWlFDdzMtRmdUSW9iM1BmTWMyaG1UMzBZN0xvVGk3cms0VWpvS1FHTmRHejhTbEwxNWRqd3JOYkc2M0tzYlRmbWZqektOc0tQZDV1UkZEVnRHemwyLWVXMVY?oc=5,AVB,,AVB stock news,130,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.3612,0.3612,0.3612,positive,0.1363636363636363,positive,2025-12-11,"[{""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""$340 Million"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 51, ""end"": 63}]","[{""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9986103773117065, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""AVB"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9151849746704102, ""start"": 23, ""end"": 26}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9962924718856812, ""start"": 117, ""end"": 130}]","[{""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""$340 Million"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AVB"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,4,0,0
2025-12-06 08:00:00,APA Corporation's (NASDAQ:APA) Share Price Boosted 25% But Its Business Prospects Need A Lift Too - simplywall.st,APA Corporation's (NASDAQ:APA) Share Price Boosted 25% But Its Business Prospects Need A Lift Too&nbsp;&nbsp;simplywall.st,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPMVlFMjNiZHFJc29MVU53dGJZWVVYS3FLQlRpN2dvMUhsbmxmaVNJQVQ5U0lSdFdJd1RieXp4X09xNTlyVWRsVkRFS0RaWVJnM095dmpBX3RtNXpMZVUtLW85aHk2UDJXdF96cC05TWVaNV83NVA2M29ENHNnemdPMVpsalF6Wm5VTGRleF8zc2tTZlo0eS1ISENQcG4waHZXUU81YWxQckZCUGRWb3dyd3VRSngzYnNZTVpV0gHAAUFVX3lxTE1xcDhjVzhEc2J6SFR0bXpHQ19JNXdpRkJUcVNfZFVkSGhyQkhiM3NBUE1PR2JNREZ1emIzdnoyNTI1SmM4Sk1lY0Z1NDA3WW1QeTFZNEt4QjZieE10Mm0xMnI3RFh4LTNRclVYR3pLc2lDdnNDNDZoV0NOSmE1R0lDYXRmVHk0dGFKUi1NSnBJLWZjSFdFLThxaURwU1NFNFd5VmVMTW5uTjZ6SUVKX3l0Zl9fNkFpaWRwMUpCYTVGRQ?oc=5,APA,,APA stock news,122,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.631,0.631,0.631,positive,0.0,neutral,2025-12-06,"[{""text"": ""APA Corporation's"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 17}, {""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 26, ""end"": 29}, {""text"": ""Share Price"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""start"": 31, ""end"": 42}, {""text"": ""25%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""start"": 51, ""end"": 54}]","[{""text"": ""APA Corporation"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9991929531097412, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""AP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8802200555801392, ""start"": 26, ""end"": 28}]","[{""text"": ""APA Corporation's"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Share Price"", ""label"": ""PERSON"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""25%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""APA Corporation"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",6,4,1,0
2025-12-04 08:00:00,"American Tower (NYSE: AMT) sets $1.70 quarterly payout payable February 2, 2026 - Stock Titan","American Tower (NYSE: AMT) sets $1.70 quarterly payout payable February 2, 2026&nbsp;&nbsp;Stock Titan",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxQcnFySWZ0bWRBT1lOUXhmS0pKUzEweDA0ZnIyS2R4WV9NYTE2RDdJWTV0UzV2ZFAwZ00wa1JvOXNOUVNuV0sxZzlySDRlZHRhMGltV010dXJ3R19HUGN3Vm1JVHdXYnIyUG1jVlZLUG00SWhqMkpGTkxkdk1aanJWanFZNHZ5WTZyUmJxTXJZeF90X1J3UDdQRXU2eXdldXps?oc=5,AMT,,AMT stock news,102,13,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2025-12-04,"[{""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 14}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 16, ""end"": 20}, {""text"": ""1.70"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 33, ""end"": 37}, {""text"": ""quarterly"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 38, ""end"": 47}, {""text"": ""February 2"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 63, ""end"": 73}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 97, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9693483710289001, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 14}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.733741044998169, ""start"": 97, ""end"": 102}]","[{""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""1.70"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""quarterly"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""February 2"", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""American Tower"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",8,4,0,1
2025-11-19 08:00:00,"AvalonBay Communities (NYSE: AVB) Announces $1.75 Q4 Dividend, Payable Jan. 15 - Stock Titan","AvalonBay Communities (NYSE: AVB) Announces $1.75 Q4 Dividend, Payable Jan. 15&nbsp;&nbsp;Stock Titan",Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxOUG9aendJYnhkaHJjRF9WN1dsQ2hkMGc5NVZKdUJfUXZvbkl4M0xLallVVTdkaWlrTnBKYW5ub0tweTROT3B2M1FKeW1mSnV6UmRWTy1BSExVRmZ0b3FyS2Y1WUQ1WDgwSHpPeHVQM3NKVnd2VVNPOEdpY2xlN19UeG5kSmJUbnd1RTNfZDh6aVJnNFFOSEJtX2pRbHJmcEdVYlY5RHY1ZXYzZV9lb3c?oc=5,AVB,,AVB stock news,101,12,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,neutral,0.0,0.0,0.0,neutral,0.0,neutral,2025-11-19,"[{""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 21}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 23, ""end"": 27}, {""text"": ""1.75"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""start"": 45, ""end"": 49}, {""text"": ""Jan."", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""start"": 71, ""end"": 75}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""start"": 96, ""end"": 101}]","[{""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9979500770568848, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 21}]","[{""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""NYSE"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""1.75"", ""label"": ""MONEY"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Jan."", ""label"": ""DATE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Titan"", ""label"": ""GPE"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""AvalonBay Communities"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",6,3,0,1
2025-11-08 08:00:00,Why APA (APA) Is Up 5.2% After Returning to Profitability and Raising Production Guidance - Yahoo Finance,Why APA (APA) Is Up 5.2% After Returning to Profitability and Raising Production Guidance&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibkFVX3lxTE1VSHhRWXA1OFNyblh6Vlh0aE1iUU8yazFMLV9qZ0w4Q3VPNmlUQWQtbVRyZlVBYnVpeGtQaW45TnYzbE84UWNwTi1VdmhmM3F1Z0VsRVZUSnROang1ZHZUNjIxak1ZQmdwclRDZkNn?oc=5,APA,,APA stock news,114,15,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.2732,0.2732,0.2732,positive,0.0,neutral,2025-11-08,"[{""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 4, ""end"": 7}, {""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 9, ""end"": 12}, {""text"": ""5.2%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""start"": 20, ""end"": 24}, {""text"": ""Returning to Profitability and Raising Production Guidance&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 31, ""end"": 114}]","[{""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8359951972961426, ""start"": 4, ""end"": 7}, {""text"": ""AP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.8017861843109131, ""start"": 9, ""end"": 11}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.995735228061676, ""start"": 101, ""end"": 114}]","[{""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""5.2%"", ""label"": ""PERCENT"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Returning to Profitability and Raising Production Guidance&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""APA"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""AP"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",7,6,0,0
2025-11-04 08:00:00,Bombardier (TSX:BBD.B): Assessing Current Valuation After Notable Share Price Gains - Yahoo Finance,Bombardier (TSX:BBD.B): Assessing Current Valuation After Notable Share Price Gains&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance,Google News,https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxObTJnejVmcXFaZ0VoN09ER01NRmNMQnExMkhvWnkycFRzbXpHZHFZbVRsQXFVaEVvcTdMUTh4SnBGTnhycmJGX1hDbTI2WWp2WFdvc1JHTHU5UFI4M09SeFpUWGxZcUNjMzRiY1RkSWlDV0N0U216cURYLW1qcnNxdXJB?oc=5,BBD,,BBD stock news,108,11,2026-01-18 18:10:41.105671,positive,0.296,0.296,0.296,positive,0.25,positive,2025-11-04,"[{""text"": ""Bombardier"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 0, ""end"": 10}, {""text"": ""TSX"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""start"": 12, ""end"": 15}, {""text"": ""Assessing Current Valuation After Notable Share Price Gains&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""start"": 24, ""end"": 108}]","[{""text"": ""Bomb"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.5498421788215637, ""start"": 0, ""end"": 4}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""score"": 0.9949071407318115, ""start"": 95, ""end"": 108}]","[{""text"": ""Bombardier"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""TSX"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Assessing Current Valuation After Notable Share Price Gains&nbsp;&nbsp;Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""WORK_OF_ART"", ""source"": ""spacy""}, {""text"": ""Bomb"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}, {""text"": ""Yahoo Finance"", ""label"": ""ORG"", ""source"": ""bert""}]",5,4,0,0
